<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CodeList xmlns="urn:fdc:difi.no:2017:vefa:structure:CodeList-1">
    <Title>ISO 6523 ICD list</Title>
    <Identifier>ICD</Identifier>
    <Agency>The International Organization for Standardization (ISO)</Agency>
    <Code>
        <Id>0002</Id>
        <Name>System Information et Repertoire des Entreprise et des Etablissements: SIRENE</Name>
        <Description>The Sirene number is used in France mainly for the official registration in the
            Trade Register and as the only number used between authorities and organizations, and
            between authorities when dealing with data interchange on organizations. Issuing agency:
            Institut National de la Statistique et des Etudes Economiques, (I.N.S.E.E.), Departement
            des Repertoires, 18, Bd Adolphe Pinard, 75675 PARIS Cedex 14, Tel: 540 1212, Tlx:204924
            INSEE F</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0003</Id>
        <Name>Codification Numerique des Etablissments Financiers En Belgique</Name>
        <Description>Many financial institutions have more than one code number, e.g. to indicate
            each branch individually. The codes can be reallocated over the time (mostly in the case
            where a financial institution terminates its activity). Some code numbers are currently
            unused. Code numbers 990 through 999 are reserved. Issuing agency: Association Belge des
            Banques, rue Ravenstein 36, Bte 5, 1000 BRUXELLES, Tel: 02 512 5868</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0004</Id>
        <Name>NBS/OSI NETWORK</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: National Bureau of
            Standards, Bldg 225 Room B151, Gaithersburg MD, 20899, USA, Tel: 301 975 2833, Tlx:
            197674 NBS UT</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0005</Id>
        <Name>USA FED GOV OSI NETWORK</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: National Bureau of
            Standards, Bldg 225 Room B151, Gaithersburg MD, 20899, USA, Tel: 301 975 2833, Tlx:
            197674 NBS UT</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0006</Id>
        <Name>USA DOD OSI NETWORK</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: Defense Communication
            Agency, DSEC - R130, 1860 Wiehle Ave, Reston VA, 22090-5500, Tel: 703 437-2802, Fax: 703
            437-2382</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0007</Id>
        <Name>Organisationsnummer</Name>
        <Description>The third digit in the organisation number is never lower than 2 in order to
            avoid it being confused with personal numbers. Issuing agency: The National Tax Board,
            (Riksskatteverket, RSV), 171 94 SOLNA, SWEDEN, Tel: 08 981520</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0008</Id>
        <Name>LE NUMERO NATIONAL</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: Ministere De L'interieur et de la Fonction Publique, Cite
            administrative de l'Etat, Tour des Finances, Bd. Pacheco. 19 - Bte 20, 1010
            Bruxelles.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0009</Id>
        <Name>SIRET-CODE</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: DU PONT DE NEMOURS (FRANCE) S.A. 137, rue de l'Universite,
            F-75334, PARIS Cedex 07, Tel: 1 45 50 65 50</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0010</Id>
        <Name>Organizational Identifiers for Structured Names under ISO 9541 Part 2</Name>
        <Description>The organizational codes established under this coding systems constitute the
            registered organizational identifiers recognised under ISO 9541-2. That standard
            effectively establishes agreements under which, as allowed by clauses 5.1 and 5.3 of ISO
            6523, both the ICD and the organization name are generally omitted, from the SIO, and
            thus only the organization code portion of the SIO is interchanged. Issuing agency:
            Association for Font Information Interchange: AFII, 2961 Copa de Oro, Los Alamites,
            California 90720, USA, Tel: 1 213 333 4642, Fax: 1 213 333 4664</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0011</Id>
        <Name>International Code Designator for the Identification of OSI-based, Amateur Radio
            Organizations, Network Objects and Application Services.</Name>
        <Description>Specific object and attribute naming conventions are currently being defined.
            Issuing agency: The Radio Amateur Telecommunications Society, 206 North Vivyen Street,
            Bergenfield, New Jersey 07621, Tel: 201-387-8896</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0012</Id>
        <Name>European Computer Manufacturers Association: ECMA</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: European Computer Manufacturers Association, rue du Rhone
            114, 1204 Geneva, SWITZERLAND Tel: 41 22 735 36 34, Tlx 22288 ECMA CH</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0013</Id>
        <Name>VSA FTP CODE (FTP = File Transfer Protocol)</Name>
        <Description>The code serves the addressing between the communicating partners Issuing
            agency: Verband der Automobilindustrie e.V. Westendstrasse 61, 6000 Frankfurt/M.1,
            GERMANY, Tel: 0 69 75 702 81, Tlx: 411293</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0014</Id>
        <Name>NIST/OSI Implememts' Workshop</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the Workshop naming and addressing tree.
            Issuing agency: United States Department of Commerce, National Institute of Standards
            and Technology, Gaithersburg, Maryland 20899, USA, Tel: 301 975 2833, Tlx:
            197674</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0015</Id>
        <Name>Electronic Data Interchange: EDI</Name>
        <Description>Details not received yet Issuing agency: Avon Rubber p.l.c. Bath Road,
            Melksham, Wiltshire, SN12 8AA, Tel: 0225 703101, Fax: 0225 707880</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0016</Id>
        <Name>EWOS Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>a) In the SIO the Organization Name will normally be omitted, b) The code is
            primarily intended for the registration of Objects Identifiers according to ISO 8824:
            Level 1: iso (1), Level 2: identified-organization (3), Level 3: ewos (0016), Level 4:
            and higher: (defined by EWOS conventions) Issuing agency: EWOS (European Workshop for
            Open Systems), Rue de Stassart 36, B-1050 Brussels, BELGIUM, Tel: 32 2 511 7455, Fax: 32
            2 511 8723</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0017</Id>
        <Name>COMMON LANGUAGE</Name>
        <Description>Codes for named populated places, geographic places, geopolitical places,
            outlaying areas, and other related entities of the state of the United States, provinces
            and territories of Canada, countries of the world, and other, unique areas. Also for the
            identification of organizations, places, equipment and governmental entities by the
            telecommunication industry. Issuing agency: Data Communications Technology Planning,
            Telcordia, Room 1F-359, 331 Newman Springs Road, P O Box 7020, Red Bank, NJ 07701-7020,
            USA, Tel: 1 201 758 2198, Fax: 1 201 530 6875</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0018</Id>
        <Name>SNA/OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form the initial part of the OSI Network addressing and
            naming tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: International
            Business Machines Corporation: IBM, IBM Bldg. 678, 1001 Winstead Drive, Cary, NC 27513,
            USA, Tel: 1 919 301 4004</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0019</Id>
        <Name>Air Transport Industry Services Communications Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: International Air Transport
            Association, IATA Centre, Route de l'Aeroport 33, P.O.Box 672, CH-1215 Geneva 15
            Airport, Switzerland</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0020</Id>
        <Name>European Laboratory for Particle Physics: CERN</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8348. Issuing agency: European Laboratory for
            Particle Physics, CERN, 1211 Geneva 23, Switzerland. Tel: 41 22 767 6111, Fax: 41 22 767
            7155</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0021</Id>
        <Name>SOCIETY FOR WORLDWIDE INTERBANK FINANCIAL, TELECOMMUNICATION S.W.I.F.T.</Name>
        <Description>To be used for assignment of object identifiers (ISO 8824/8825) Issuing agency:
            SOCIETY FOR WORLDWIDE INTERBANK FINANCIAL, TELECOMMUNICATION S.W.I.F.T. Avenue Adele,1,
            B - 1310 La Hulpe, BELGIUM, Tel: +32 2 6553111, Fax: +32 2 6553226</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0022</Id>
        <Name>OSF Distributed Computing Object Identification</Name>
        <Description>OSF provides public domain software in OS, ISO networking and management. The
            initial use of the coding system are for identifying the following objects in OSF's
            distributed computing environment: the attributes of entries in the distributed
            directory, the object class of each entry in the directory, the type of name components
            (RDNs), the communication protocol profiles, the interfaces offered by Issuing agency:
            Open Software Foundation, 11 Cambridge Center, Cambridge, MA 02142, USA, Tel: 617 621
            8700, Fax: 617 621 0631</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0023</Id>
        <Name>Nordic University and Research Network: NORDUnet</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and tree as
            depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8348. Issuing agency: NORDUnet, c/o SICS, P O Box 1263,
            S-16428 KISTA, Sweden, Tel. +46 8 7521563, Fax. +46 8 7517230</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0024</Id>
        <Name>Digital Equipment Corporation: DEC</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing as described
            in ISO8348 Addendum 2. Issuing agency: Digital Equipment (Europe) S.A.R.L. B.P. 129 -
            Sophia Antipolis, 06561 Valbonne Cedex, France, Tel: 33 92 95 51 11, Fax: 33 93 65 34
            24</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0025</Id>
        <Name>OSI ASIA-OCEANIA WORKSHOP</Name>
        <Description>The code is used as an element of object identifiers which need to be assigned
            relating the ISPs (International Standardized Profiles) that AOW is working on. Issuing
            agency: OSI ASIA-OCEANIA WORKSHOP, c/o Interoperability Technology Association for
            Information Processing, Japan, Sumito Gaien Bldg. 3F, 24 Daikyo-cho, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo
            160, JAPAN, Tel: +81-3-3358-2721, Fax: +81-3-3358-4753</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0026</Id>
        <Name>NATO ISO 6523 ICDE coding scheme</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8348 Issuing agency: North Atlantic Treaty
            Organisation (NATO), NATO HQ, Bvd Leopold III, B - 1110 Brussels, Belgium, Attention: Mr
            S Seiffert, DS/ICP Section, (TSGCEE SG/9 Secretary), Tel: 010 32 2 728 4632, Fax: 010 32
            2 728 4103</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0027</Id>
        <Name>Aeronautical Telecommunications Network (ATN)</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the ISO network addressing and naming
            tree as depicted in Addendum No 2 to ISO 8348 Issuing agency: International Civil
            Aviation Organization (ICAO), Communications Section, Air Navigation Bureau, 1000
            Sherbrooke Street West, Montreal, Quebec H3A 2R2, CANADA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0028</Id>
        <Name>International Standard ISO 6523</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: Styria Federn GmbH, Postfach 101, A-8750 Judenburg,
            AUSTRIA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0029</Id>
        <Name>The All-Union Classifier of Enterprises and Organisations</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: General Computing Centre of the State, Committee of the
            USSR on Statistics, 44 Izmailovskoye Chosse, Moscow 105679, U S S R</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0030</Id>
        <Name>AT&amp;T/OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network,
            addressing and naming tree as specified in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency:
            AT&amp;T, Standards and Regulatory Support, Room 5A256, Route 202-206N, Bedminster, NJ
            07921, UNITED STATES OF AMERICA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0031</Id>
        <Name>EDI Partner Identification Code</Name>
        <Description>To identify EDI partners Issuing agency: Odette NL, Europaplein 2, 1078 GZ
            AMSTERDAM, Tel: 020 - 5491212, Fax: 020 - 6463857</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0032</Id>
        <Name>Telecom Australia</Name>
        <Description>The code is used as an element of Object Identifier when defining objects
            within Telecom Australia. In addition the code shall be used as an element of NSAP
            addressing. Issuing agency: Australia Telecommunications Corporation, Forward Network
            Planning Unit, 11/172 Williams Street, Melbourne, AUSTRALIA 3000, Tel: 613 634 7878,
            Fax: 613 670 2562</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0033</Id>
        <Name>S G W OSI Internetwork</Name>
        <Description>Exclusive use by S G W Issuing agency: S G Warburg Group Management Ltd, 1
            Finsbury Avenue, LONDON, EC2M 2PA, Tel: 071 606 1066, Fax: 071 382 4800</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0034</Id>
        <Name>Reuter Open Address Standard</Name>
        <Description>To be used in the formation of OSI Network Service Access Point (NSAP)
            addresses Issuing agency: Reuters Ltd, 85 Fleet Street, LONDON, EC4P 4AJ, Tel: 071 250
            1122, Tlx: 23222</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0035</Id>
        <Name>ISO 6523 - ICD</Name>
        <Description>This code will be used internationally by BP thus a non-geographic code is
            requested. Issuing agency: The British Petroleum Co Plc, Britannic House, 1 Finsbury
            Circus, LONDON, EC2M 7BU, Tel: 071 496 4054, Fax: 071 496 4540, Tlx:
            888811</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0036</Id>
        <Name>TeleTrust Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>a) In the SIO the Organization name will normally be omitted. b) The code is
            primarily intended for the registration of Object Identifiers for security related
            objects according to ISO/IEC 8824, Level 1: iso(1), Level 2: identified-organization(3),
            Level 3: teletrust(0036), Level 4 and higher: (defined by TeleTrust conventions) Issuing
            agency: TeleTrust Deutschland e.V. c/o GMD, Dolivostrasse 15, D-6100 Darmstadt, GERMANY,
            Tel: 49 6151 869 700, Fax: 49 6151 869 785</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0037</Id>
        <Name>LY-tunnus</Name>
        <Description>It is possible to add 0-4 characters set to the code for more detailed use of
            one organization. Characters are digits or capital letter. Issuing agency: National
            Board of Taxes, (Verohallitus), Haapanimenk 7-9B, SF-00530 Helsinki, FINLAND Tel: 010
            3580 39621, Fax: 010 3580 39624247</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0038</Id>
        <Name>The Australian GOSIP Network</Name>
        <Description>As noted above it will be used as the initial identifier of an NSAP coding
            scheme. Issuing agency: Standards Australia, 80 Arthur Street, P O Box 458, North
            Sydney, NSW 2059, AUSTRALIA, Tel: 010 612 963 4111, Fax: 010 612 959 3896</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0039</Id>
        <Name>The OZ DOD OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI naming and addressing, tree as
            depicted in ISO 8348/Add 2 standard. Format of the tree is described in the Australian
            GOSIP Manuals and used globally. Issuing agency: The Australian Department of Defence,
            Communications and Information Branch, Russell Offices (B-3-25), P O Box E33, Queen
            Victoria Terrace, Canberra, ACT 2600, AUSTRALIA, Tel: 010 616 265 3730, Fax: 010 616 265
            3601</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0040</Id>
        <Name>Unilever Group Companies</Name>
        <Description>To be used in data communications to form part of the Network Address as
            defined in ISO 8348. The ISO 6523, ICD IDI format with Binary syntax will be used.
            Issuing agency: Information Technology Group, Unilever Plc, Unilevr House, P O Box 68,
            LONDON, EC4P 4BQ, Tel: 071 822 6763, Fax: 071 822 5996</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0041</Id>
        <Name>Citicorp Global Information Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form the initial part of the Citicorp Network addressing
            object identifier tree and naming tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348 Issuing
            agency: Citicorp Global Information Network, One Court Square, 48th floor, Long Island
            City, NY 11120, USA, Tel: 1 718 248 2990, Fax: 1 718 248 2767</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0042</Id>
        <Name>DBP Telekom Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>1) The ICD is primarily intended for the registration of Object Identifiers,
            according to ISO 8824/8825 (ANS.1) to be used for the identification resp. registration
            of: - application layer protocols, - file &amp; document formats, - information objects,
            - local/remote procedures. The OID structure and the inclusion of the ICD therein is
            given below: level 1: iso(1), level 2: identifiedOrganisation(3), level 3 (ICD):
            dbpt(0042), level 4 to n: (defined by Telekom) Issuing agency: DBP Telekom, Product
            Development Telesec, P.O. Box 10 00 20, D - 5900 Siegen, GERMANY, Tel: +49 271 708 1600,
            Fax: +49 271 21 835</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0043</Id>
        <Name>HydroNETT</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing as depicted
            in ISO 8348/AD2. Issuing agency: Norsk Hydro a.s. Att. Nils Hoeg, Corporate Staff
            Information Systems, Drammensveien 264, Vaekero, Oslo, P. O. Box 200, N-1321 Stabekk,
            Norway, Tel: +47 2 73 81 00, Fax: +47 2 73 97 87, Tlx: 72948 hydro N</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0044</Id>
        <Name>Thai Industrial Standards Institute (TISI)</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of international addressing for Thailand.
            Issuing agency: Thai Industrial Standards Institute (TISI), Rama VI Street, Bangkok
            10400, THAILAND TEL: +66 2 245 78 02, FAX: +66 2 247 87 41</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0045</Id>
        <Name>ICI Company Identification System</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will be used to manage NSAP allocation for all ICI companies on a
            worldwide basis. The organisation code is used Worldwide by ICI application systems to
            identify ICI registered companies in machine to machine communications. Issuing agency:
            ICI PLC, Millbank, London, SW1P 3JF, Tel: 071 834 4444, Fax: 071 834 2042</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0046</Id>
        <Name>FUNLOC</Name>
        <Description>Current applications are Philips accounting and logistic systems; new
            application is the identification of objects in the open network environment according
            to ISO 8824 which starts with a party identification Issuing agency: Royal Philips
            Electronics N.V. Corporate Information Technology, building VP-1, Groenewoudseweg 1, P O
            Box 218, 5600 MD Eindhoven, The Netherlands, Tel: +31 40 27 83008, Fax: +31 40 27
            80080</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0047</Id>
        <Name>BULL ODI/DSA/UNIX Network</Name>
        <Description>To be used in data communications to form part of the network address. The ISO
            6523 ICD IDI format with binary syntax will be used. Issuing agency: BULL S.A. DTBG,20
            Rue Dleumegaie, FRANCE 93406 Saint-Ouen, Tel: +33 (1) 49 45 51 40, Fax: +33 (1) 49 45 53
            36</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0048</Id>
        <Name>OSINZ</Name>
        <Description>ISO 6523 ICD IDI format with binary syntax will be used Issuing agency: OSINZ,
            (Open Systems Interconnection of New Zealand Inc.), c/- P O Box 5356, Wellesley Street,
            Auckland New Zealand Tel: Fax</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0049</Id>
        <Name>Auckland Area Health</Name>
        <Description>ISO 6523 ICD IDI format with binary syntax will be used Issuing agency:
            Auckland Area Health Board, Information Systems, Greenlane/National Women's Hospital,
            Greenlane West, Auckland 3, New Zealand Tel: Fax</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0050</Id>
        <Name>Firmenich</Name>
        <Description>Interconnect the plants by an OSI network essentially over X.25 carrier Issuing
            agency: Firmenich S A, 7, rue de la Bergere, CH-1217 Meyrin 2, GENEVA, Switzerland Tel:
            ++41 22 780 2211, Contact: Marc Gaudar</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0051</Id>
        <Name>AGFA-DIS</Name>
        <Description>Medical Communication Issuing agency: AGFA N.V. Septestraat 27, 2640 Mortsel,
            BELGIUM, Tel: + 32 3 4442111, Fax: + 32 3 4447094</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0052</Id>
        <Name>Society of Motion Picture and Television Engineers (SMPTE)</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also be used to identify SMPTE constituent organizations
            (committees, working groups, task forces, etc./), and the objects they, define. The ICD
            code will also form the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network addressing and naming
            tree as specified in Addendum 2 tot ISO 8348 Issuing agency: Society of Motion Picture
            and Television Engineers (SMPTE), 595 W. Hartadae Ave. White Plains, NY 10607, USA, Tel:
            +1 914 761 11 00, Fax: +1 914 761 31 15</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0053</Id>
        <Name>Migros_Network M_NETOPZ</Name>
        <Description>NONE Issuing agency: Migros-Genossenschafts-Bund, Administration KIM-TEKO HH17,
            Limmatstrasse 152, 8031 ZURICH, Tel: Fax</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0054</Id>
        <Name>ISO6523 - ICDPCR</Name>
        <Description>This code could be used internationally by Pfizer thus a non-geographic code is
            required. The code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing and naming tree
            depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8348. Issuing agency: Pfizer Central Research, Ramsgate
            Road, Sandwich, Kent, CT13 9NJ, Tel: 0304 616223, Fax</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0055</Id>
        <Name>Energy Net</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: ABB Asea Brown Boveri Ltd, Affolterstrasse 44, 8050
            Zurich, Correspondence Address: ABB Informatik AG, C. Falbriad, TEC1.N, Haselstrasse,
            CH-5401 Baden, Tel: + 41 56 75 26 77, Fax: + 41 56 75 21 21</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0056</Id>
        <Name>Nokia Object Identifiers (NOI)</Name>
        <Description>a) In the SIO the organization name will normally be omitted, b) The code is
            primarily intended for the registration of Object Identifiers according to ISO/IEC 8824:
            Level 1:iso(1), Level 2:identified-organization(3), Level 3:nokia(xxxx), Level 4 and
            higher:defined by Nokia conventions Issuing agency: Nokia Corporation Tel: + 358 0
            43761, Research Centre Fax: + 358 0 4376227, P.O.Box 156, SF-02101 Espoo,
            FINLAND</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0057</Id>
        <Name>Saint Gobain</Name>
        <Description>To be used for assignment of: N.E.T (ISO 8348/Add 2), A.E.T (FTAM, X.400 Psaps,
            and so on), and object identification (ISO 8824/8825) Issuing agency: Saint Gobain, Les
            Miroirs, 18, avenue d'Alsace, 92096 PARIS La Defense Cedex 27, Monsieur Jean Dorleans,
            Tel: 33 1 47 62 36 05, Fax: 33 1 47 62 50 64</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0058</Id>
        <Name>Siemens Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will form the initial part of the OSI Network addressing and
            naming tree as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348 (Network layer addressing). These
            addresses will uniquely identify systems within SCN and to the outside world. Issuing
            agency: Siemens AG,RI SCN, St Martin-Str. 76, W-8000 Muenchen 90, Germany, Tel: +49 89
            4133 2565, Fax: +49 89 4133 1984</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0059</Id>
        <Name>DANZNET</Name>
        <Description>NONE Issuing agency: DANZAS AG, Head Office, Switzerland 4051 Basel, Attn
            Schutz Bertrand</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0060</Id>
        <Name>Data Universal Numbering System (D-U-N-S Number)</Name>
        <Description>The D-U-N-S Number originated to facilitate the compilation of financial status
            reports on those involved in business transactions but it is now widely used for other
            purposes also. The number has world wide recognition as a means of identifying
            businesses and institutions. Issuing agency: Dun and Bradstreet Ltd, Holmers Farm Way,
            High Wycombe, 1 Bucks, HP12 4UL</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0061</Id>
        <Name>SOFFEX OSI</Name>
        <Description>This code is to assist in uniquely identifying data network node addresses in
            an international supporting network for financial applications. This supporting network
            may have operational interfaces to other (private) data networks. Issuing agency: SOFFEX
            Swiss Options and Financial Futures Exchange AG. Neumattstrasse 7, CH-8953 Dietikon,
            Switzerland</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0062</Id>
        <Name>KPN OVN</Name>
        <Description>This code is used in the VTOA network of KPN OVN. Issuing agency: Koninklijke
            KPN, Operator Vaste net BBT/IP, P O Box 30000, 2500 GA'sGravenhage, The Netherlands,
            Contact: G L J Kloos, Tel: +31 70 343 4762, Fax: +31 70 371 3569, E-mail:
            g.l.j.kloos@kpn.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0063</Id>
        <Name>ascomOSINet</Name>
        <Description>- Issuing agency: Ascom AG, Belpstrasse 37, CH-3000 Bern, Switzerland Fax: +41
            55 41 63 85, Tel: +41 55 41 60 04</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0064</Id>
        <Name>UTC: Uniforme Transport Code</Name>
        <Description>The code identifies an individual transport or handling unit (e.g. pallet,
            parcel) for reasons of tracing or tracing. The unit may have an international
            destination. Issuing agency: Foundation UTC, P.O.Box 82118, 2508 EC The Hague, The
            Netherlands, Tel: + 31 70 35 10 777, Fax: + 31 70 35 12 025</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0065</Id>
        <Name>SOLVAY OSI CODING</Name>
        <Description>Whenever possible, ISO 8348 addresses using this code will comply with FIPS PUB
            146, with an End System ID of exactly 4 octets, so that the DSP can also conform to ECMA
            117 where ECMA's subnet-address maps onto FIPS's Subnet ID concatenated with the End
            System ID. Issuing agency: Direction Centrale Technique (Informatique Scientifique),
            SOLVAY S.A, Rue de Ransbeek 310, B-1120 Bruxelles</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0066</Id>
        <Name>Roche Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>Will be used internationaly by Roche thus a non-geographic code is required.
            Issuing agency: F. HOFFMANN - LA ROCHE AG, Grenzacherstasse 124, CH-4002 BASEL,
            Switzerland</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0067</Id>
        <Name>ZellwegerOSINet</Name>
        <Description>BAKOM - Switzerland Issuing agency: Zellweger Uster AG, Wilstrasse 11, CH-8610
            USTER, Switzerland Tel: + 41 1 943 2608, Fax: + 41 1 943 3815</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0068</Id>
        <Name>Intel Corporation OSI</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will be used to form the Initial Domain Identifier (IDI) portion
            of the Initial Domain Part (IDP) as described in ISO 8348 Addendum 2 for OSI NSAP
            addressing. Issuing agency: Intel Corporation, 1900 Prairie City Road, Folsom, Ca.
            95630, USA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0069</Id>
        <Name>SITA Object Identifier Tree</Name>
        <Description>SITA intends to use its OID Tree to define its own Objects for use with its
            OSI-based services (e.g. MHS &amp; OSI Management) Issuing agency: SITA, 112 Avenue
            Charles de Gaulle, 92522 NEUILLY-SUR-SEINE CEDEX, France</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0070</Id>
        <Name>DaimlerChrysler Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will form the initial part of the OSI Network addressing and
            naming free as depicted in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348 (Network Layer addressing). These
            addresses will uniquely identify systems within DBCN and to the outside world. Issuing
            agency: DaimlerChrysler AG, TOS/L, 010 M406, Emil0Kessler Strasse 4, 70546 Stuttgart,
            GERMANY</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0071</Id>
        <Name>LEGO /OSI NETWORK</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network
            addressing and naming tree as specified in addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency: LEGO
            Systems Inc, 555 Taylor Road, Enfield, Conneticut 06082, USA, Tel: (203) 749 2291, Fax:
            (203) 763 6681</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0072</Id>
        <Name>NAVISTAR/OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form the Initial Domain Part of the OSI Network
            addressing and naming tree as specified in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348. Issuing agency:
            International Truck &amp; Engine Corp, 4201 Winfield Road, Warrenville, Illinois 60555,
            USA, Attention: Kosit Manaspiti, Tel: 630 753 5517, Fax: 630 753 6710, e-mail:
            kosit.manaspiti@nav-international.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0073</Id>
        <Name>ICD Formatted ATM address</Name>
        <Description>Used as an ATM address prefix by, 1) Newbridge ATM terminal equipment: a) when
            performing user - network address registration, b) transparently initiating signalled
            ATM connections on behalf of other non-ATM (LAN) devices, c) directly initiating
            signalled ATM connections, 2) Newbridge ATM switching equipment used to: a) perform
            network - user address registration, b) perform routing of Switched Virtual Connections
            across a private ATM cell switching network Issuing agency: Newbridge Networks
            Corporation, 600 March Road, P O Box 13600, Kanata, Ontario, CANADA, K2K
            2E6</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0074</Id>
        <Name>ARINC</Name>
        <Description>ARINC will define its own Objects for use with its OSI-based systems and
            services. ARINC will also define Objects for use within the Aeronautical industry.
            Issuing agency: ARINC Incorporated, 2551 Riva Road, Annapolis, MD 21401-7465, USA, Tel:
            + 410 266 4000, Fax: + 410 266 4040</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0075</Id>
        <Name>Alcanet/Alcatel-Alsthom Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network addressing scheme as
            depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8384 Issuing agency: Alcatel Network Services Deutschland
            GmbH, Motostr. 25, D - 70499 Stuttgart, GERMANY, Technical Contact: Thomas Galuschka,
            Tel: + 49 711 821 2367, Fax: + 49 711 821 4793</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0076</Id>
        <Name>Sistema Italiano di Identificazione di ogetti gestito da UNINFO</Name>
        <Description>To be used for assignments of object identifiers according to ISO 8824 and ISO
            8825 Issuing agency: UNINFO, Ente di Normazione Federato all'UNI, C.so Galileo Ferraris
            93, 10128 Torino, ITALY, Tel: + 3911 501 027, Fax: + 3911 501 837</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0077</Id>
        <Name>Sistema Italiano di Indirizzamento di Reti OSI Gestito da UNINFO</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code forms the initial part of the OSI network Addressing and naming
            tree depicted in Addendum 2 of ISO 8348. Issuing agency: UNINFO, Ente di Normazione
            Federato all'UNI, C.so Galileo Ferraris, 93, 10128 Torino, ITALY</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0078</Id>
        <Name>Mitel terminal or switching equipment</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will form the initial part of the naming tree for: 1 - Private
            Integrated Services Network manufacturer-specific information as the Organization
            identifier forming the initial part of the OBJECT IDENTIFIER tree. 2 - OSI Application
            Layer such as CSTA (ECMA 179). Issuing agency: Mitel Corporation, 350 Legget Drive, P O
            Box 13089, Kanata ON K2K 1X3, Canada, Attn: Mr Francois Audet</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0079</Id>
        <Name>ATM Forum</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form part of the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network
            addressing as specified in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348 Issuing agency: The ATM Forum, 303
            Vintage Park Drive, Foster City, CA 94404-1138, USA, Tel: +(415)-578-6860, Fax:
            +(415)-525-0182</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0080</Id>
        <Name>UK National Health Service Scheme, (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>EDIRA recommendations for coding in EDIFACT and other EDI systems Issuing
            agency: National Health Service, Information Management Center, 15 Frederick Road,
            Birmingham, B15 1SD, Contact person: Mr Brian LOVE, Tel: +44 1454 261 551, Fax: +44 1454
            261 581</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0081</Id>
        <Name>International NSAP</Name>
        <Description>None Issuing agency: Federal Office for Communications, Zukunfstrasse 44,
            POSTFACH, CH-2501 Biel, Switzerland Tel: +41 32 285 111, Fax: +41 32 285
            528</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0082</Id>
        <Name>Norwegian Telecommunications Authority's, NTA'S, EDI, identifier scheme (EDIRA
            compliant)</Name>
        <Description>For use in EDIFACT messages in accordance with current national recommendation
            on identification of EDI objects. (EDIRA compliant) Issuing agency: Norwegian
            Telecommunications Authority, P O Box 447 Sentrum, N-0104 Oslo, NORWAY, Contact person:
            Mr Knut Smaaland Tel: + 47 22 82 48 04, Fax: + 47 22 82 48 40</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0083</Id>
        <Name>Advanced Telecommunications Modules Limited, Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>The ICD code will also form part of the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network
            addressing as specified in Addendum 2 to ISO 8348 Issuing agency: ATM Ltd, Mount
            Pleasant House, Cambridge, CB3 0BL, ENGLAND</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0084</Id>
        <Name>Athens Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industry Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>EDIRA recommendations for coding in EDIFACT and other EDI syntaxes. Issuing
            agency: Athens Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industry, Akadimias Street 7, GR 108 71 Athens,
            Contact person: Mrs M Hliapa, Tel: +301 362-7911, Fax: +301-362-4643</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0085</Id>
        <Name>Swiss Chambers of Commerce Scheme (EDIRA) compliant</Name>
        <Description>merical identifiers of organizations EDIRA recommendations for coding in
            syntaxes used for e-commerce and egovernment, e.g. EDIFACT, ebXML Issuing agency: Zurich
            Chamber of Commerce on behalf of Swiss Chambers, of Commerce, CH-8022 Zurich, Otto
            Mueller, Phone: + 411 217 4050 Fax: + 411 217 4051, e-mail:
            omueller@zurichcci.ch</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0086</Id>
        <Name>United States Council for International Business (USCIB) Scheme, (EDIRA
            compliant)</Name>
        <Description>EDIRA recommendations for coding in EDIFACT and other EDI syntaxes. Issuing
            agency: United States Council for Internationa Business (USCIB), 1212 Avenue of the
            Americas, USA New York, NY 10036, Contact person: Mr Peter ROBINSON, Tel: +1212 354
            4851, Fax: +1212 575 0327</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0087</Id>
        <Name>National Federation of Chambers of Commerce &amp; Industry of Belgium, Scheme (EDIRA
            compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: National Federartion of Chambers of Commerce &amp; Industry of,
            Belgium Avenue des Arts 1-2. B 10, BE 1040 Brussels, Contact person: Mr Michael
            PEEREMAN, Tel: +322-217-3671, Fax: +322-217-4634</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0088</Id>
        <Name>EAN Location Code</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: EAN International, rue Royale 29, B-1000 Brussels, Belgium,
            Tel: +32.2.218.76.74, Fax: +32.2.218.75.85</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0089</Id>
        <Name>The Association of British Chambers of Commerce Ltd. Scheme, (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: The Association of British Chambers of Commerce Ltd. 9, Tufton
            Street, Westminster, LONDON, SW1P 3QB, Contact person: Mrs Elizabeth Boyd-Adams, Tel:
            +44 71 222 1555, Fax: +44 71 799 2202, E-mail X400 G=Elizabeth, S=BoydAdams, O= ABCC,
            A=BT, C=GB</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0090</Id>
        <Name>Internet IP addressing - ISO 6523 ICD encoding</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Internet Assigned Numbers Authority, c/o Joyce K. Reynolds, USC
            - Information Sciences Institute, 4676 Admiralty Way, Marina del Rey, California
            90292-6695, USA, E-mail: iana @ isi.edu, Phone: +1 310-822-1511</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0091</Id>
        <Name>Cisco Sysytems / OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Cisco Systems, 170 W. Tasman Drive, San Jose, CA 95134, USA,
            Phone + 1 408 526 4000, Fax + 1 408 426 4100</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0093</Id>
        <Name>Revenue Canada Business Number Registration (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Revenue Canada, 123 Slater Street, Ottawa, ON K1A OL8,
            Signatory name, Roderick G. Quiney, Director-General, Contact address, 25 McArthur,
            Tower C, 7th Floor, Ottawa, Ontario CANADA K1A OL8, Tel + 1 613 941 5007, Fax + 1 613
            941</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0094</Id>
        <Name>DEUTSCHER INDUSTRIE- UND HANDELSTAG (DIHT) Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Deutscher Industrie -und Handelstag (DIHT), Adenauerallee 148,
            D - 53113 Bonn, Contact person: Ute Quink-Ermst, Tel: + 49 228 104 102, Fax: + 49 228
            104 158</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0095</Id>
        <Name>Hewlett - Packard Company Internal AM Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Hewlett - Packard Company, 3000 Hanover Street, Palo Alto CA
            94304, USA, Phone +1 415 424 3600, Fax +1 415 424 3632</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0096</Id>
        <Name>DANISH CHAMBER OF COMMERCE Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Danish Chamber of Commerce, Boerson, DK 1217 Copenhagen,
            Contact person: Mr Vagn JENSEN, Tel: + 45 33 95 05 00, Fax: + 45 33 32 52
            16</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0097</Id>
        <Name>FTI - Ediforum Italia, (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: FTI - Ediforum Italia, Viale Lazio, 21, 20135 Milano - ITALY,
            Contact person: Mr Giorgio PACIFICI, Tel: + 39 2 545 61 20, Fax: + 39 2 551 35 44,
            E-mail: FTI@mbox.cosi.it</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0098</Id>
        <Name>CHAMBER OF COMMERCE TEL AVIV-JAFFA Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Chamber of Commerce Tel Aviv-Jaffa, 84 Hahashmonaim Street, Tel
            Aviv 67011, ISRAEL, Contact person: Mr Zvi AMIT, General Manager, Tel: +972 3 563 1010,
            Fax: +972 3 561 9025</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0099</Id>
        <Name>Siemens Supervisory Systems Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Siemens AG, ON S, Ruppert-Mayer-Str. 44, D-81359 Munchen,
            Germany, Tel: +49 89 722 23555, Fax: +49 89 722 26473</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0100</Id>
        <Name>PNG_ICD Scheme</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: GPT Limited, Public Networks Group, New Century Park, P O Box
            53, Coventry, CV3 1HJ, Tel. 01203-562-000. (Contact - 'Strategy/Customer Network
            Services').</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0101</Id>
        <Name>South African Code Allocation</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Thawte Consulting, 33 Protea Way, Durbanville 7550, South
            Africa</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0102</Id>
        <Name>HEAG</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Hessische Elektrizitats-AG, Jagertorstrasse 207, 64289
            Darmstadt, Germany, Technical Contact : Peter Giesendorf Tel 049 6151 709 2528, Gerd
            schmidt Tel 049 6151 709 2547, Andreas Prels Tel 049 6151 709 2529, Fax 049 6151 709
            2420</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0104</Id>
        <Name>BT - ICD Coding System</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Tony Holmes, pp 9.4, 207 Old Street, London, EC1V 9NR, Tel: +44
            171 250 6981</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0105</Id>
        <Name>Portuguese Chamber of Commerce and Industry Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Portuguese Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Rua das Portas de
            Santo Antao, 89, PT 1194 Lisboa Codex, Contact person: Mr Antonio REGUENGOS, Tel: +351 1
            342 4111, Fax: +351 1 342 4304, E-mail (X.400)
            c=pt;a=marconisva;p=email400;0=acl-ccip;s=drc; 0u=drc</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0106</Id>
        <Name>Vereniging van Kamers van Koophandel en Fabrieken in Nederland (Association of
            Chambers of Commerce and Industry in the Netherlands), Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Vereniging van Kamers van Koophandel en Fabrieken in Nederland
            Watermolenlaan, 1, NL 3447 GT Woeden, Contact person: Drs. G. C. KNOOP, Tel: +31 348 42
            69 11, Fax: +31 348 42 12 31</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0107</Id>
        <Name>Association of Swedish Chambers of Commerce and Industry Scheme (EDIRA
            compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Association of Swedish Chambers of Commerce and Industry, P O
            Box 16050, SE 10321 Stockholm, Sweden, Contact person: Mr Tell HERMANSON, Tel: +46 8 613
            1800, Fax: +46 8 411 2432, E-mail: stock@chamber.se</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0108</Id>
        <Name>Australian Chambers of Commerce and Industry Scheme (EDIRA compliant)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Australian Chambers of Commerce and Industry, P O Box E 14,
            Queen Victoria Terrace, AU Canberra ACT 2600, Australia, Contact person: Mr Brent DAVIS,
            Tel: +61 6 273 23 11, Fax: +61 6 273 31 96</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0109</Id>
        <Name>BellSouth ICD AESA (ATM End System Address)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: BellSouth Corporation, 1155 Peachtree Street NE, Atlanta, GA
            30309, Contact: Robert V. Epley, Tel: + 404-332-2216, Fax: + 404-420-8477</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0110</Id>
        <Name>Bell Atlantic</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Bell Atlantic, 1310 N. Courthouse Rd. 3rd Floor, Arlington, VA
            22201, Tel: +703- 974-1510, Fax: +703-974-0616</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0111</Id>
        <Name>Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, PO Box 1331,
            445 Hoes Lane, Piscataway, NJ 08855, USA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0112</Id>
        <Name>ISO register for Standards producing Organizations</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: International Organization for Standardization (ISO), 1 rue de
            Varembe, Case Postale 56, CH 1211 Geneve 20, SWITZERLAND</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0113</Id>
        <Name>OriginNet</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Origin BV, Groenewoudse weg 1, 5621 BA Eindhoven, The
            Netherlands, Tel: +31 4027 87295, Fax: +31 4027 89081</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0114</Id>
        <Name>Check Point Software Technologies</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Check Point Software Technologies Ltd, 3A Jabotinski st.
            Diamond Tower, RamatGan 52520, ISRAEL, Tel: +972 3613 1833, Fax: +972 3575
            9256</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0115</Id>
        <Name>Pacific Bell Data Communications Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Pacific Bell, Broadband Strategy and Engineering, 2600 Camino
            Ramon, Room 1S200BB, San Ramon, CA 94583, USA, Phone: +510-823-3578, Fax:
            +520-867-</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0116</Id>
        <Name>PSS Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: PSS (Postal Security Services), c/o Finland Post Ltd, Products,
            Electronic Messaging, P.O. Box 702, FIN-00100 POSTI, FINLAND Tel: +358 204 511,
            Fax:</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0117</Id>
        <Name>STENTOR-ICD CODING SYSTEM</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: B. Sambasivan, Stentor Resource Centre Inc. Room 480, 160 Elgin
            St. Ottowa, Ontario K1G 3JA, Canada, Tel.# + 1 613 781 7458 Fax.# + 1 613 781
            6454</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0118</Id>
        <Name>ATM-Network ZN'96</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Deutsche Telekom AG, AM Kavalleriesand 3, 64295
            Darmstadt</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0119</Id>
        <Name>MCI / OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: MCI Telecommunications Corporation, Technical Standards
            Management, Dept. 1225/107, 2400 N. Glenville Dr. Richardson, TX 75082, USA, Phone
            +1.972.918.5630, Fax +1.972.918.6038</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0120</Id>
        <Name>Advantis</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Advantis, Charles M. Reiss, 231 N. Martingdale Rd, Schaumbur,
            Ill, USA, 60173- 2254, Phone: 847-240-8504, Fax: 847-240-3864</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0121</Id>
        <Name>Affable Software Data Interchange Codes</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Affable Software Corporation, 6239 Thome Avenue, Burnaby,
            British Columbia, Canada- V3N 2V2, Contact: Eric Kolotyluk Tel: +1-604
            522-1201</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0122</Id>
        <Name>BB-DATA GmbH</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: BB-DATA GmbH, Brunnestrasse 11, 13355 Berlin, Germany, Contact:
            Dirk Haegebarth, Tel: +49 30 2455 4353, Fax; +49 30 2455 7201</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0123</Id>
        <Name>BASF Company ATM-Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: BASF Computer Services GmbH, Carl-Bosch-Str. 38, 67056
            Ludwigshafen, Germany, (Contact: BCS/NET Tel. + 49621 60 49323)</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0124</Id>
        <Name>IOTA Identifiers for Organizations for Telecommunications Addressing using the ICD
            system format defined in ISO/IEC 8348</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: DISC, British Standards Institution, 389 Chiswick High Road,
            London W4 4AL, UK</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0125</Id>
        <Name>Henkel Corporate Network (H-Net)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Henkel KgaA, Dep: SIS/BC-Networks, 40191 Dusseldorf, Germany,
            Contact: Christopher Heidler Uwe Wirtz, Tel: + 49 211 797 9400 Tel: +49 211 797 5500,
            Fax: + 49 211 798 19400 Fax: +49 211 798 1110</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0126</Id>
        <Name>GTE/OSI Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: GTE, Industry Standards, HQW02J85, 700 Hidden Ridge, Irving, TX
            75038, USA, Phone: + 972 718 6291, Fax: + 972 718 4393</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0127</Id>
        <Name>Dresdner Bank Corporate Network</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Dresdner Bank AG, IT-Kommunikationssysteme, Windmuehlstr. 14,
            60329 Frankfurt am Main, Germany, Contact: Peter Radig, Tel: + 49 69 263 7243, Fax: + 49
            69 263 5510, Email: Peter.Radig@Dresdner-Bank.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0128</Id>
        <Name>BCNR (Swiss Clearing Bank Number)</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Telekurs AG, Hardturmstrasse 201, CH - 8021 Zurich, Switzerland
            Tel +41.1.279.2111</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0129</Id>
        <Name>BPI (Swiss Business Partner Identification) code</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Telekurs AG, Hardturmstrasse 201, CH - 8021 Zurich, Switzerland
            Tel +41.1.279.2111</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0130</Id>
        <Name>Directorates of the European Commission</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: European Commission, Information Directorate, Data Transmission
            Service, Rue de la Loi, 200, B-1049 Brussels, Belgium</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0131</Id>
        <Name>Code for the Identification of National Organizations</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: China National Organization Code Registration Authority, Center
            (CNRAC), No 46. East Door, Dewai Yu Zhong Xi Li, Xicheng District, Beijing, P.R. of
            China, 100029, Tel. + 86 10 6202 4549, Fax. + 86 10 6202 4513</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0132</Id>
        <Name>Certicom Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Certicom Corp, Suite 1050, 1400 Fashion Island Blvd, San Mateo,
            CA 94404, U.S.A. Tel: 650 312 7960, Fax: 650 312 7969</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0133</Id>
        <Name>TC68 OID</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: ISO TC68, Banking and Related Financial Services, c/o American
            Bankers' Association, 1120 Connecticut Ave, N.W. Washington, DC 20036, USA, Tel: 1-
            (202) 663 5284, Fax: 1- (202) 828 4540</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0134</Id>
        <Name>Infonet Services Corporation</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Infonet NV/SA, Av. Louise 350 Box 3, 1050 Brussels, Belgium,
            Attn: Mr Mircea Pisica - Senior System Engineer, E-mail: Mircia_Pisica@infonet.com, Tel:
            +322 627 3900, Fax: +322 646 1308</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0135</Id>
        <Name>SIA Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: SIA-Societ Interbancaria per l'Automazione S.p.A. Viale
            Certosa, 218, I-20156 Milano, ITALIA, Tel. +39-02-3005.1, Fax:
            +39-02-38003333</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0136</Id>
        <Name>Cable &amp; Wireless Global ATM End-System Address Plan</Name>
        <Description>Issuing agency: Cable &amp; Wireless Global Business Inc. 8230 Boon Boulevard,
            Vienna, Virginia 22182, USA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0137</Id>
        <Name>Global AESA scheme</Name>
        <Description>nstruct and Administer AESAs, Routing of ATM switched connections Use to from
            globally unique Global One ICD AESAs Issuing agency: Global One, Park Atrium, Rue des
            Colonies, 11, B-1000 Brussels, Belgium, Tel + 322 545 2000 Fax + 322 545
            2005</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0138</Id>
        <Name>France Telecom ATM End System Address Plan</Name>
        <Description>e coding system will be used to provide ATM End System Addresses based on ICD
            format NSAP addresses. These addresses will be used to uniquely identify User Network
            Interfaces to ATM networks as specified by the ATM Forum UNI specifications. France
            telecom will also use these addresses Internally and to provide worldwide customers with
            non- Geographic private AESAs. These global addresses should be Reachable by non-France
            Telecom ATM users via Interconnecting ATM carriers. The ICD Code will also form part of
            the Initial Domain Part of the OSI network addressing as specified in Addendum 2 to ISO
            8348 Issuing agency: France Telecom, BRX/DAP/AFC, 6 place d'Alleray, 75505 Paris Cedex
            15, France, Tel + 331 4444 2775 Fax + 331 4444 2437, e-mail:
            alain.bidron@francetelecom.fr</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0139</Id>
        <Name>Savvis Communications AESA:.</Name>
        <Description>obal Addressing of Savvis ATM Switches and any direct customer ATM networks for
            implementation of PNNI Used to form a globally unique Savvis ICD ATM End System Address
            Issuing agency: Savvis Communications, Contact: Gary Rubel, 717 Office Parkway, St
            Louis, MO 63141-7115, Tel: - +314-468-4104 (Direct), +314-468-7030 (Main), Fax: -
            +314-468- 7050</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0140</Id>
        <Name>Toshiba Organizations, Partners, And Suppliers' (TOPAS) Code</Name>
        <Description>e purpose of this coding system is to identify organizations world-wide that
            have business or technical transactions with Toshiba Corporation in terms of ISO 13584
            Parts Library standard based electronic catalogue interchange service. The interchange
            is not limited to those between a member organization and Toshiba Corporation.
            Interchanges between member organizations based on the organization identifier of this
            coding system are also in scope. Reference to this organization identification code in
            other business transactions is also allowed Reference to this organization identifier in
            other business transactions is also possible provided the organizations concerned are
            registered as members of the Issuing agency: Toshiba Corporation, 1-1 Shibaura, 1-Chome,
            Minato-Ku, Tokyo, 105-8001, Japan. Request for a TOPAS Code, Attention to: TOPAS
            Administration, Technology Planning, Division, Person Responsible: Dr. Akinobu Kasami,
            Corporate Executive Vice President and Director, Contact Person for this application and
            technical issues: Mr. Hiroshi Murayama, Human Interface Laboratory, Toshiba Corporate
            Research and Development Centre, Address: 1, Komukai Toshiba-cho, Saiwai-ku,
            Kawasaki-shi, 212-8582, Japan, Email: hiroshi.murayama@toshiba.co.jp, TEL :(+81)
            44-549-2397 FAX: (+81) 44-520-1308</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0141</Id>
        <Name>NATO Commercial and Government Entity system</Name>
        <Description>identify all Commercial and Governmental entities that provide material and/or
            services to the Armed Forces of the NATO nations and several non-NATO nations
            (Sponsored) around the world. This information is used by NATO and Sponsored nations'
            Logisticians to identify Commercial and Government Entities they deal with. This
            Information is used by all functions of Logistics support such as Acquisition, Sourcing,
            EDI, Re-Provisioning, Material Management, etc. Determination of the real source for an
            item of supply is one of the most important prerequisites for proper application of the
            Uniform System of Item Identification within NATO. It is the source where documentation
            will be obtained from and its location normally gives advice for codification
            responsibility. Within the NATO Codification System the term Manufacturer covers the
            whole range of possible sources of technical data for items entering the supply chains
            or participating, countries. The primary use of manufacturers coding is in ADP
            operations related to support management programs such as material management
            codification, standardization, etc. Issuing agency: NATO Group of National Director on
            Codification (AC/135), NATO Maintenance and Supply Agency, 11 Rue de la Gare, L-8302
            Capellen, G. D. Luxembourg, Attn: Secretary to AC/145, LZ-C Programme</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0142</Id>
        <Name>SECETI Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>e function as the 'Application Centre' for the Italian National Interbank
            Network, having been authorized by the Bank of Italy, and the Italian Banking
            Association to operate in that capacity. The scheme is intended for the registration of
            object identifiers according to ISO 8824 and ISO 8825 The code is primarily intended for
            the registration of Object Identifiers according to ISO 8824/8825, Level 1: ISO (),
            Level 2: identified -organization (), Level 3: SECETI S.p.A. (), Level 4: and higher:
            (defined by SECETI conventions), The contact person is Dr. Elvezio Montesarchio, e-mail:
            elvezio.montesarchio@seceti.it Issuing agency: Servizi Centralizzati SECETI S.p.A. Via
            Zurigo, 3-20147 Milano, ITALY, Tel: +39-02- 48310.1, Fax: +39-02-48310206</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0143</Id>
        <Name>EINESTEINet AG</Name>
        <Description>itially the Network covers the geographical area of Germany with the intention
            of expanding into all the European countries EINSTEINet's goal is to provide Application
            Services using an ATM network to customers located throughout Europe. The need for the
            international ATM address structure is to serve EINSTENet's customers with consistent
            ATM addresses from end-to-end. Issuing agency: EINSTEINet AG, Ramskamt 71-75, 25337
            Elmshorn, Germany, Contact: Jrg Peeck or Michael Wiesmann, Tel: + 49 4121 403 000,
            Email: j.peeck@einstenet.de / m.wiesmeann@einsteinet.de</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0144</Id>
        <Name>DoDAAC (Department of Defense Activity Address Code)</Name>
        <Description>code assigned to uniquely identify all military units in the United States
            Department of Defense. None Issuing agency: DoD (Unites States Department of Defense),
            Defense Logistics Management Standards Office, DLMSO (J-763), Suite 1834, 8725 John J.
            Kingman Road, Fort Belvoir, VA 22060-6217, USA, Contact: Mr Jackie Carter, Tel: +1 703
            767 0684 fax: +1 703 767 0161, e-mail: jackie_carter@dlmso.hq.dla.mil</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0145</Id>
        <Name>DGCP (Direction Gnrale de la Comptabilit Publique)administrative accounting
            identification scheme</Name>
        <Description>de assigned by the French public accounting office None Issuing agency: DGCP
            (Direction Gnrale de la Comptabilit Publique), 139 Rue de Bercy, 75572 Paris Cedex
            12, France</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0146</Id>
        <Name>DGI (Direction Gnrale des Impots) code</Name>
        <Description>ench taxation authority None Issuing agency: DGI (Direction Gnrale des
            Impots), Bureau G2, Teledoc 971, 92 Allee de Bercy, 75574 Paris Cedex 12,
            France</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0147</Id>
        <Name>Standard Company Code</Name>
        <Description>Partner identification code which is registered withJIPDEC/ECPC. None Issuing
            agency: Japan Information Processing Development Corporation, / Electronic Commerce
            Promotion Center (JIPDEC/ECPC), Time 24 Bldg. 10F, 2-45 Aomi, Koto-ku, Tokyo 135-8073,
            Japan, Contact: Kazuhiko Wakaizumi, Tel: +813 5500 3643, Fax: 813 5500 3660, E-mail:
            waka@ecom.or.jp</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0148</Id>
        <Name>ITU (International Telecommunications Union)Data Network Identification Codes
            (DNIC)</Name>
        <Description>ta Network Identification Codes assigned by the ITU. None Issuing agency: ITU
            (International Telecommunications Union), Telecommunication Standardization Bureau
            (TSB), Place des Nations, CH-1211 Geneva 20, Switzerland Tel: +4122 730 5222, Fax: +4122
            730 5853, E-mail: geng-sheng.li@itu.int, Web: www.itu.int,
            www.itu.int/itudoc/itu-t/ob-lists</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0149</Id>
        <Name>Global Business Identifier</Name>
        <Description>r a company's ability to obtain complete and accurate information about
            potential suppliers Used to identify and designate in electronic commerce Issuing
            agency: ResolveNet (IOM) Ltd, Atlantic House, 2nd Floor, Circular Road, Douglas, Isle of
            Man IMI ISQ, UK, Laura J Jany, Tel: 001 610 625 4160 Fax; 001 610 625 4180</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0150</Id>
        <Name>Madge Networks Ltd- ICD ATM Addressing Scheme</Name>
        <Description>e code will be used as part of an ATM NSAP addressing scheme for the
            establishment of PVC and SPVC connections Addressing for Madge Networks global ATM
            network and the connections of any Madge Customers requiring the allocation of ATM
            addresses from Madge Networks. Issuing agency: Madge Networks, Wexham Springs, Framewood
            Road, Wexham, Slough, SL3 6PJ, Tel: +44 1753 661 575 Fax: + 44 1753 661 114 e-mail:
            steve.irving@madge.co</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0151</Id>
        <Name>Australian Business Number (ABN) Scheme</Name>
        <Description>e ABN will be a unique identifier for a business to interact with Government
            (Commonwealth, State and Local) throughout, Australia and is the supporting number for
            the Goods and Service Tax (GST). The Legislation covering the use of ABN, (see notes on
            use) will have application throughout the Commonwealth of The ABN is established by: A
            New Tax System (Australian, Business Number) Act 1999, enacted by the Australian
            Parliament. The scheme is expected to last for at least 100 Years without reallocation
            of identification numbers. The ABN is specified in English. Issuing agency: Australian
            Taxation Office, 140 Creek Street, Brisbane Q 4000, AUSTRALIA. Postal Address: GPO Box
            8022, Brisbane Q 4000, AUSTRALIA</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0152</Id>
        <Name>Edira Scheme Identifier Code</Name>
        <Description>r the unambiguous identification of registration scheme used in e-commerce (not
            to be used for the identification of organizations) The code is used to designate
            unambiguously schemes used in e-commerce to specify any entity but organizations Issuing
            agency: EDIRA Association, c/o Zurich chamber of commerce, Bleicherweg 5, P. O. Box
            4031, CH-8022 Zurich, Switzerland Otto Mueller OttoMueller-omueller@zurichcci.ch, Phone
            + 411 217 4050; Fax + 411 217 4051, Andre Mesropian, EDIRA Executive Director,
            Phone/Fax: +33 1 6023 0504, E-mail: amesropi@club-internet-fr</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0153</Id>
        <Name>Concert Global Network Services ICD AESA</Name>
        <Description>Global Addressing of the Concert ATM switches and any direct customer ATM
            networks for implementation of PNNI. It will also be used for any attached carrier ATM
            networks. Used to form globally unique Concert ICD ATM End System Addresses (AESA's)
            Issuing agency: Concert Global Network Services Ltd, Sir John Swan Building, 26 Victoria
            Street, Hamilton, HM12 Bermuda, Contact: John Haynes, Tel: +44 (0) 20 7876 4225, Fax:
            +44 (0) 20 7876 4419, E-mail: john.haynes@concert.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0154</Id>
        <Name>Identification number of economic subjects: (ICO)</Name>
        <Description>ique identification of economic subjects for all administrative purposes The
            identification number ICO is used in the Czech Republic mainly in all administrative
            acts (tax system, banking system, statistics. etc.) Issuing agency: Czech Statistical
            Office, Sokolovsk 142, 186 04 Praha 8- Karlin, Czech Republic, Mr Staniv Palas, Tel: +
            420 274 0525 75, Fax: + 420 268 326 80, e-mail: palas@qw.czso.cz</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0155</Id>
        <Name>Global Crossing AESA (ATM End System Address)</Name>
        <Description>nstruction, administration and implementation of a scalable AESA schema for
            routing if ATM switched connections. ICD will be used as a component of the IDP (Initial
            Domain Part) for OSI addressing Issuing agency: Global Crossing Ltd, Wessex House, 45
            Reid Street, Hamilton HM-12, Bermuda, Contact: Joseph DeVita, Global Crossing Ltd, 1
            Bausch &amp; Lomb Place, Suite 400, Rochester, NY 14604 USA, Tel: + 1 716 777 1093, Fax:
            + 1 716 546 4387</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0156</Id>
        <Name>AUNA</Name>
        <Description>lecommunication network of operators in the AUNA Group This code shall be used
            as an element of NSAP addressing Issuing agency: AUNA, Dept: Direccin corporativa dr
            red, Responsibility: Ana Isabel Fernndez Herndez, Paeso Castellana 83-85. 28046-
            Madrid (Spain). Tel: +34 91 202 5808, Fax: +34 91 202 5173</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0157</Id>
        <Name>ATM interconnection with the Dutch KPN Telecom</Name>
        <Description>O Drager Net The ICD code also form the initial part of the OSI network
            addressing scheme (Addendum 2 of ISO 8384) Issuing agency: Informatie en Communicatie
            Technologie Organisatie, Odijkerweg 25, 3972 NE Driebergen, Contact: A Knol - Head DCB,
            Tel: + 31 (0) 343 534 500, Fax: + 31 (0) 343 534 999</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0158</Id>
        <Name>Identification number of economic subject (ICO) Act on State Statistics of 29 November
            2001,  27</Name>
        <Description>e unique identification of economic subjects (legal persons and natural
            personsentrepreneurs) used for registration The identification number ICO is used in
            Slovakia in almost all administrative acts (tax system, banking system, statistics,
            etc.) Issuing agency: Slovak Statistical Office, Mileticova 3, 824 67 Bratislava, Slovak
            Republic, Mr Ivan Lieskovsk, tel.: + 421 2 502 36 250, Fax: + 421 2 5556 1541, email:
            ivan.lieskovsky@statistics.sk</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0159</Id>
        <Name>ACTALIS Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>e code is primarily intended for the registration of Object Identifiers (OIDs)
            according to ISO 8824/8825: Level 1: iso (1), Level 2: identified-organization (3),
            Level 3: ACTALIS SpA (0159), Level 4 and higher: (defined by ACTALIS) See "Intended
            purpose/application area" Issuing agency: ACTALIS S.p.A. Via Taramelli, 26, 20124
            Milano, ITALY, Tel: + 39 2 6084 1. The technical contact point is Ing. Adriano Santoni
            (email: adriano.santoni@sia.it; will be adriano.santoni@actalis.it after April
            2002)</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0160</Id>
        <Name>GTIN - Global Trade Item Number</Name>
        <Description>e EAN.UCC.GTIN is a globally unique identifier of trade items. A trade item is
            any item (product or service) upon which there is a need to retrieve pre-defined
            information and that may be priced, ordered or invoiced at any point in any supply chain
            The GTIN identification scheme is currently (2002) used by more than 900,000
            organizations in the world. It is widely in the consumer goods and other industries to
            identify items and packages. The GTIN can be represented in a standard bar code format.
            Issuing agency: EAN Inernational, Rue Royal 145, B-1000 Brussels, Tel: + 32 2 227 1020,
            Fax: +32 2 227 1021, e.mail: info@ean-int.org, Contact: Henri Barthel</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0161</Id>
        <Name>ECCMA Open Technical Directory</Name>
        <Description>centralized dictionary of names and definitions of trading concepts,
            essentially goods and services that are bought, sold or exchanged. This is a
            classification neutral dictionary of names and attributes (also referred to as
            characteristics or properties). The eOTD will help improve the speed and accuracy of
            Internet searches and can be imported into sourcing, procurement and ERP systems with
            minimal data transformation costs. Issuing agency: Electronic Commerce Code Management
            Association2980 Linden Street Suite E218017 BethlehemUSURL:
            http://www.eccma.orgresponsible: Yvette Thomasemail: Yvette.Thomas@Eccma.orgphone:
            001-610-861-5990fax: 001- 610-861-5992</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0162</Id>
        <Name>CEN/ISSS Object Identifier Scheme</Name>
        <Description>allocate OIDs to objects defined in the standards and specifications developed
            in CENs technical bodies (TCs, Workshops, etc) The code is primarily intended for the
            registration ofObject Identifiers according to ISO 8824-1 Annex BLevel 1: iso (1)Level
            2: identified-organization (3)Level 3: CEN (nnnn the ICD allocated)Level 4: and higher:
            (defined by CEN conventions) Issuing agency: Comit Europen de Normalization - CENRue
            de Stassart 36B-1050 Brussels</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0163</Id>
        <Name>US-EPA Facility Identifier</Name>
        <Description>provide for the unique identification of facilities regulated or monitored by
            the United States Environmental Protection Agency (EPA).A facility is a distinct real
            property entity (i.e., a man-made object and its surrounding real estate). Facilities
            incorporate the characteristics of being: (1) objects, established at (2) specific
            places, for (3) specific purposes. A facility can include monitoring stations, waste
            sites, and other entities of environmental interest that cannot be classified as single
            facilities. This is maintained within the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency Facility
            Registration System (FRS) Issuing agency: U.S. Environmental Protection AgencyMail Code
            2832T1200 Pennsylvania Avenue NWWashington, DCUSAAttn: Patrick GarveyTel: +1 202 566
            1687Fax: +1 202 566 1684Email: garvey.pat@epa.govWeb:
            www.epa.gov/enviro/html/facility.html</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0164</Id>
        <Name>TELUS Corporation</Name>
        <Description>SA Addressing Scheme for ATM PNNI Implementation ICD is required for PNNI
            implementation on TELUS ATM network in order to establish an addressing scheme for SPVC
            connections within and between regions Issuing agency: TELUS Corporation, Floor 24,
            TELUS Plaza South Tower10020 - 100 Street N.W.Edmonton, Alberta, CanadaT5J 0N5. Gregory
            Rees, greg.rees@telus.com, Tel: (780) 493-3921 Fax: (780) 421-8085</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0165</Id>
        <Name>FIEIE Object identifiers</Name>
        <Description>provide identifiers for international enterprises and organizations operating
            in fields of business served by the Jaakko Poyry Group. On the date of the application,
            these fields include Forest industry, Energy, Infrastructure and Environment. To provide
            an internationally unambiguous framework for existing coding practices in this The code
            is primarily intended for the registration of Object Identifiers according to ISO/IEC
            8824, 8825 and 11179: Level 1: iso (1) Level 2: identified organization (3) Level 3:
            fieie code (nnnn, the ICD allocated) Level 4 and higher: (defined by FIEIE conventions)
            Issuing agency: Jaakko Poyry Group Oyj PL4, Jaakonkatu 3 FIN-01621 Vantaa Finland Tel:
            +358 9 894 71 Fax: +358 9 878 1818 Email: general.jp@poyry.fi URL: http://www.poyry.com
            Contact: Mr Risto Ryyppo</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0166</Id>
        <Name>Swissguide Identifier Scheme</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify objects, esp. companies and professionals in
            directories/databases The code is used to uniquely identify the objects in the
            Swissguide directory. Issuing agency: Swissguide AG Lindenstrasse 1, 8302 Kloten
            Switzerland Attn: Juerg Dangel Tel: +41 1 444 39 39 Fax: +41 1 444 39 85 Email:
            juerg.dangel@swissguide.ch Web: www.swissguide.ch</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0167</Id>
        <Name>Priority Telecom ATM End System Address Plan</Name>
        <Description>e coding system will be used to provide ATM End System Address based on IDC
            format NSAP addresses required for Priority Telecom ATM PNNI implementation. These
            addresses will be used to uniquely identify User Network interfaces to Priority Telecom
            ATM Networks as specified by the ATM Forum UNI specifications. PT plans to use these
            addresses to connect to other public ATM networks in the countries PT is operating (The
            Netherlands, Norway and Austria) Used to form a globally unique Priority Telecom ATM End
            System Address. PT customers and interconnect with public ATM networks requires the use
            of unique AESA Issuing agency: Priority Telecom Netherlands B.V. Beech Avenue 100 1119
            PW, Schiphol-Rijk The Netherlands Contact: Roger Schobben +31 20 778 2520 / Fax: +31 20
            778 2600 Email: rschobben@prioritytelecom.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0168</Id>
        <Name>Vodafone Ireland OSI Addressing</Name>
        <Description>plementation of an ATM network in connection with 3G rollout. The code will be
            used for ATM network related addressing purposes, and for CLNS network. Issuing agency:
            Vodafone Ireland Limited, 3rd Floor, Block B, MountainView, Sandyford, Dublin 18,
            Ireland Contact:Colm Fleming, Core Network Planning Manager, Ph. +353 87 2352155 Fax
            +353 1 2037611 colm.fleming@vodafone.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0169</Id>
        <Name>Swiss Federal Business Identification Number. Central Business names Index (zefix)
            Identification Number</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify all companies/organizations registered in the Swiss Register
            of Commerce and the Swiss Central Business Names Index To uniquely identify entries in
            Swiss Central Business Names Index (zefix). The principle purpose of the zefix on
            internet is to provide a swisswide search function, and thus provide the public with a
            service to determine the legal domicile, the cantonal office for the register of
            commerce in charge, and the latters address. Issuing agency: Swiss Federal Office of
            Justice, Bundesrain 20, CH-3003 Bern (Switzerland) Tel: +41 31 322 36 32 Fax: +41 31 323
            51 52</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0170</Id>
        <Name>Teikoku Company Code</Name>
        <Description>ikoku Company Code is allocated to all incorporations, business owners,
            government organizations and other public offices in Japan. TDB (Teikoku Databank Ltd.)
            retains company codes of approximately 1.7 million companies within Japan. Teikoku
            Company Code, a unique company ID, has already been adopted by many companies both as a
            standard company code in customer data managements and as an identification code for
            online electronic commerce transactions. Since every company trades with companies
            abroad, they need to use it in their international business transaction. Therefore, it
            is desired to register TDB as an ICD to RA of the ISO/IEC 6523. None Issuing agency:
            TEIKOKU DATABANK LTD. Corporate Planning Department 2-5-20 MINAMI-AOYAMA, MINATO-KU,
            TOKYO, JAPAN TEL: 03-5775-3132 FAX: 03-5775-3127 Email:
            spinfo@mail.tdb.co.jp</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0171</Id>
        <Name>Luxembourg CP &amp; CPS (Certification Policy and Certification Practice Statement)
            Index</Name>
        <Description>dex of the Certification Policies and Certification Practice Statement issued
            by Luxembourg PKI Issuing agency: Ministry of The Economy and Foreign Trade 19-21
            Boulevard Royal L-2914 Luxembourg e-mail: Francois.Thill@eco.etat.lu Fax: +352 478
            4311</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0172</Id>
        <Name>Project Group Lists of Properties (PROLIST)</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify properties, blocks and lists of properties (LOP) for products
            and services in the process industry. The products are electrical and process control
            devices. The code is used to uniquely identify the objects in the PROLIST online
            dictionary. Issuing agency: Project Group Lists of Properties (PROLIST) c/o Bayer
            Technology Services GmbH Geb. K 9 51368 Leverkusen Germany E-Mail: Prolist@NAMUR.de Tel:
            +49 - 214 - 30 57852 Fax: +49 - 214 - 30 72774</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0173</Id>
        <Name>eCI@ss</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify properties, classes and list of characteristics (LoC) for
            products and services available in the eCI@ss classification system The code is used to
            uniquely identify objects in the eCI@ss classification system. Issuing agency: eCI@ss,
            Mr. Thorsten Hohnle Gustav-Heinemann-Ufer 84-88, 50968 Cologne Germany Email:
            hoehnle@eclass-office.com Tel: +49 (221) 4981-831 Fax: +49 (221) 4981-856</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0174</Id>
        <Name>StepNexus</Name>
        <Description>provide identifiers within StepNexus loader objects. These addresses will be
            used to uniquely identify StepNexu key usage fields within X509 certificates for use in
            the StepNexus loader scheme. Used to define unique certificate attributes within X509
            certificates Issuing agency: StepNexus, St Andrews House, The Links, Kelvin Close,
            Birchwood, Warrington, Cheshire WA3 7PB</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0175</Id>
        <Name>Siemens AG</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify properties, blocks, classes and lists of properties used or
            specified by Siemens AG - Power Generation The code is used to uniquely identify objects
            in the Siemens AG - Power Generation corporate dictionary Issuing agency: Siemens AG,
            Wolfgang-Reuter-Platz 4, 47053 Duisburg, Germany</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0176</Id>
        <Name>Paradine GmbH</Name>
        <Description>uniquely identify properties, classes,and list of properties (LoP) for products
            and services available in Paradine Reference Dictionary Systems The code is used to
            uniquely identify objects in Paradine Reference Dictionary Systems Issuing agency:
            Paradine GmbH, Prinz Eugen Strasse 70, 1040 Vienna, Austria</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0177</Id>
        <Name>Odette International Limited</Name>
        <Description>r use in EDI and other B2B exchanges in the European automotive industry to
            identify business entities (organisations). The scheme is used to identify
            organisations, and parts of organisations which are parties to or are referenced in
            automotive supply chain transactions such as EDI messaging and other B2B exchanges.
            Issuing agency: Odette International Limited, Forbes House, Halkin Street, London SW1X
            7DS</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0178</Id>
        <Name>Route1 MobiNET</Name>
        <Description>r rooting OIDs defined by Route1 Security Corporation for Route1 MobiNET.
            Intended to cover MobiNET connected organizations, Route1 Security Corporation, its
            subdivisions, customers and any organization using MobiNET or Route1's services and
            products For rooting OIDs defined by Route1 Security Corporation for Route1 MobiNET.
            Intended to cover MobiNET connected organizations, Route1 Security Corporation, its
            subdivisions, customers and any organization using MobiNET or Route1's services and
            products. The OID structure and the inclusion therein of the ICS is as follows:
            ISO.Identifiedorganization.ICD(Route1 MobiNET).AFI.PCI.Org_ID.OPI.MC Issuing agency:
            Route1 Security Corporation Attn Yamian Quintero 1920-155 University Avenue Toronto
            Ontario M5H 3B7 Canada Tel +1 416.848.8391 x2232 Fax +1 416.848.8394</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0179</Id>
        <Name>Penango Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>To identify objects, policies, and data related to Penangos products and
            services. The ICD is primarily intended for registration of Object Identifiers in
            accordance with ISO/IEC 8824 (ASN.1). Issuing agency: Penango, Inc. 1215 K Street 17th
            Floor Sacramento, CA 95814 USA Tel: +1 (888) 273-6264 Fax: +1 (888) 273-6264
            oid+icd@penango.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0180</Id>
        <Name>Lithuanian military PKI</Name>
        <Description>dex of the Certification Policies and Certification Practices Statements issued
            by Lithuanian military PKI The code is used to uniquely identify Certification Policies
            and Certification Practice Statements in Lithuanian military PKI Issuing agency: The
            Ministry of National Defence of the Republic of Lithuania, Totoriu Str. 25/3, LT-01121
            Vilnius Lithuania ATTN: Cpt. Aurelijus Andrijauskas E-mail: ssc@kam.lt Tel: +370 5
            2785225 Fax: +370 5 2735555</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0183</Id>
        <Name>Numro d'identification suisse des enterprises (IDE), Swiss Unique Business
            Identification Number (UIDB)</Name>
        <Description>To uniquely identify all companies/organizations registered in Switzerland in
            all official register (Swiss Register of Commerce, VAT register, Canton register, etc)
            The UIDB shall make lt possible to identify an enterprise quickly, unambiguously and on
            a permanent basis. The UIDB and the other identification characteristics associated with
            it shall be managed via a specific UIDB register. The main identification
            characteristics (status, address, etc.) shall be accessible to the public. Issuing
            agency: Swiss Federal Statistical Office (FSO), Espace de l'Europe 10 CH-2010 Neuchtel
            (Switzerland) Tel.: +41 32 713 85 94 Fax: +41 31 323 62 63</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0184</Id>
        <Name>DIGSTORG</Name>
        <Description>To be used for identifying Danish companies included juridical persons and
            associations in international trade It is possible to add 0-4 characters set to the code
            for more detailed use of one organization. Characters are digits or capital letter.
            Issuing agency: The Danish Agency for Digitisation Landgreven 4 Postboks 2193 DK-1017
            Copenhagen K Denmark Tel: +45 33 92 52 00 E-mail: digst@digst.dk</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0185</Id>
        <Name>Perceval Object Code</Name>
        <Description>Intended to uniquely identify in an international context any physical and or
            abstract entities related to Perceval products and services using Abstract Syntax
            Notation One in accordance with ISO/IEC 8824 The ICD is primarily intended for
            registration and resolution of Object Identifiers in accordance with ISO/IEC 8824 with
            reduced encoding size and non-geographic context Issuing agency: Perceval SA, Tenbosch
            9, 1000 Brussels, Belgium Mr Henri-Jean Pollet, E-mail hjp@perceval.net Tel +32 2 640
            9194, Fax +32 2 640 3154</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0186</Id>
        <Name>TrustPoint Object Identifiers</Name>
        <Description>To uniquely identify objects and mechanisms globally throughout communications
            networks using TrustPoint security products and services Issuing agency: TrustPoint
            Innovation Technologies, Attn: Sherry Shannon-Vanstone, 816 Hideaway Circle East, Unit
            244 Marco Island, FL 34145 USA http://www.trustpointinnovation.com Tel: +1 905 302 6929
            Email: sviconsulting@aol.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0187</Id>
        <Name>Amazon Unique Identification Scheme</Name>
        <Description>To provide identifiers for properties, classes, groups, or lists of data and
            objects specified by or used by Amazon.com, Inc. and its Affiliates Identifiers assigned
            under this scheme may be usable as Object Identifiers in accordance with ISO/IEC 8824,
            usable with Directories in accordance with ISO/IEC 9594, usable in accordance with
            ISO/IEC 8348, or usable in other contexts as defined by Amazon. Issuing agency: Amazon
            Technologies, Inc. Post Office Box 8102 Reno, Nevada 89507-8102 United States Contact:
            Peter Bowen Tel: +1 206 266 1000 E-mail: auis-info@amazon.com</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0188</Id>
        <Name>Corporate Number of The Social Security and Tax Number System</Name>
        <Description>The number system of Japan is a social infrastructure to improve efficiency and
            the transparency of the social security and the tax system, and to achieve a highly
            convenient, impartial, and fair society. Additionally, the profit of the number system
            can be free usage for various purposes, so we want to use the Corporate Number as
            identifiers in various fields, like in electronic commerce, transportation, etc. The
            preliminary work, numbering the identifiers for the beginning of usage in January 2016,
            is being done. Issuing agency: National Tax Agency Japan 3-1-1 Kasumigaseki, Chiyoda-ku,
            Tokyo 100-8978, JAPAN Telephone: +81 3 3581 5451 E-mail: kokuzei-houjinbangou@nta.go.jp
            Point of Contact: Tadahisa Kodaira</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0189</Id>
        <Name>European Business Identifier (EBID)</Name>
        <Description>For use in EDI or other B2B exchanges to identify business entities
            (organizations). The scheme is used to identify organisations, and parts of
            organisations which are parties to or are referenced in electronic transactions such as
            EDI messaging or other B2B exchanges. Issuing agency: EBID Service AG CAS-Weg 1-5 76131
            Karlsruhe Germany E-mail: kontakt@unternehmensverzeichnis.org Phone: +49
            721-9638-300</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0190</Id>
        <Name>Organisatie Indentificatie Nummer (OIN)</Name>
        <Description>The OIN is part of the Dutch standard Digikoppeling and is used for identifying the organisations that take part in electronic message exchange with the Dutch Government. The OIN must also be included in the PKIo certificate.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0191</Id>
        <Name>Company Code (Estonia)</Name>
        <Description>Company code is major and only unique identifier of all institutions and organisations in Estonia. This code is widely used for various purposes, including electronic commerce. Usage of company code is required in communication between institutions and also in communication between private and public organisations. 
            For use in EDI or other B2B (B2C) exchanges to identify private and public organisations. 
            Issuing agency: Centre of Registers and Information Systems of the Ministry of Justice, Lkke 4, 19081 Tallinn, Estonia
            E-mail: rik@just.ee
          </Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0192</Id>
        <Name>Organisasjonsnummer</Name>
        <Description>Identify entities registered in the Central Coordinating Register for
            Legal Entities in Norway. The scheme with ICD code + organization number will be used to
            identify organisations that are parties to or referenced in electronic
            transactions such as electronic invoicing or other B2B exchanges. Issuing agency: The Brnnysund Register Centre,
            Havnegata 48, N0-8900 Brnnysund</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0193</Id>
        <Name>UBL.BE Party Identifier</Name>
        <Description>Identification and addressing of different parties involved in
            invoicing. Issuing agency: UBL.BE, 161, Drve Richelle, bote 71, B-1410 Waterloo, Belgium
            E-mail: info@ubl.be
            </Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0195</Id>
        <Name>Singapore Nationwide E-lnvoice Framework</Name>
        <Description>For use in electronic messages in accordance to the Singapore
            nationwide e-invoice framework on Identification of organization. Issuing agency: Infocomm Media Development Authority, 10 Pasir Panjang Road #03-01, Mapletree Business City, Singapore 117438
        </Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0196</Id>
        <Name>Icelandic identifier - slensk kennitala</Name>
        <Description>Identification of Icelandic individuals and legal entities. Issuing agency: For individual, identifiers starting with 0 to 3
            Icelandic National Registry, www.skra.is
            For legal entities, identifiers starting with 4 to 9
            Directorate of Internal Revenue, www.rsk.is</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0199</Id>
        <Name>Legal Entity Identifier (LEI)</Name>
		<Description>The LEI is the global, open identifier established at the urging of the Financial Stability Board and the recommendation of the G20. The LEI is established as the ISO 17442 standard, is governed by the LEI Regulatory Oversight Committee (LEI-ROC) and has been implemented by the Global Legal Entity Identifier Foundation (GLEIF). The LEI code connects to key reference information that enables clear and unique identification of legal entities participating in financial transactions. Each LEI contains information about an entity's ownership structure and thus answers the questions of 'who is who' and 'who owns whom'. Simply put, the publicly available LEI data pool can be regarded as a global directory, which greatly enhances transparency in the global marketplace. Already applied very broadly within financial regulation and rapidly being adopted for KYC and a number of other purposes in financial markets, the LEI is set to spread into a range of other fields, including trade facilitation, business reporting and supply chain management.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0200</Id>
        <Name>Legal entity code (Lithuania)</Name>
		<Description>For use in EDI (electronic data interchange) for C2B and others exchanges to identify legal entities.</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0201</Id>
        <Name>Codice Univoco Unit Organizzativa iPA</Name>
		<Description>Used to identify uniquely all organizational units of public bodies, authorities and public services in Italy</Description>
    </Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0202</Id>
        <Name>Indirizzo di Posta Elettronica Certificata</Name>
		<Description>Used to identify senders and receivers of certified electronic mail as defined by Italian law</Description>
	</Code>
    <Code>
        <Id>0203</Id>
        <Name>eDelivery Network Participant identifier</Name>
		<Description>Used as an electronic address identifier for participants within a secure data communication network.</Description>
		</Code>
	<Code>
        <Id>0204</Id>
        <Name>eDelivery Network Participant identifier</Name>
		<Description>Identification of Public Authorities.</Description>
    </Code>
</CodeList>
